Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Commercial Recordings Collection AIA.031.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: 78 RPM Records, circa 1903-1959; 2734 sound discs
  - Side A: MacGregor, Scotty, "Fou the Nou" [44] Side B: MacGregor, Scotty, "Annie Laurie" [41] (Musette No.1) (Disk XA78 874)
  - Side A: MacGregor, Scotty, "It's Nice to Get Up in the Morning" [42] Side B: MacGregor, Scotty, "Loch Lomond" [45] (Musette No.2) (Disk XA78 875)
  - Side A: MacGregor, Scotty, "Stop Your Tickling, Jock" [40] Side B: MacGregor, Scotty, "Old Rustic Bridge" [43] (Musette No.3) (Disk XA78 876)
  - Side A: MacGregor, Scotty, "Song of the Cave" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: MacGregor, Scotty, "Don't Forget Me" [Matrix # not listed] (Top Music E2-KB-4893) (Disk XA78 877)
  - Side A: MacLeod, Bobby and His Band, "Hamilton House" [M.3256] Side B: MacLeod, Bobby and His Band, "Flowers of Edinburgh" [M.3257] (Beltona BL.2611) (Disk XA78 1437)
  - Side A: MacLeod, Jean, "Mist Covered Mountains of Home; The Cockle Gatherer" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: MacLeod, Jean, "Road to the Isles" [Matrix # not listed] (Thistle T-224B) (Disk XA78 816)
  - Side A: MacPhee, James, "Sa Choill Ud Thall " [OEA.14025] Side B: MacPhee, James, "Suas U A Chaidhlig " [OEA.14026] (His Master's Voice B.9800) (Disk XA78 815)
  - Side A: Magee, Charlie, "Between Me and You" [G-1009] Side B: Magee, Charlie, "Patsy Dargon" [G-1010] (Glenside W-151) (Disk XA78 826)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph, "Hello Patsy Fagan" [73878] Side B: Maguire, Joseph, "Far From Erne's Shore" [73880] (Decca 12261) (Disk XA78 797)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph, "Corrigan" [64417] Side B: Maguire, Joseph, "Wicklow Mountain High" [63996] (Decca 12168) (Disk XA78 830)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph, "Boy From Ballytore" [64200] Side B: Maguire, Joseph, "Milestone" [64201] (Decca 12188) (Disk XA78 831)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph, "Hello Patsy Fagan" [73878] Side B: Maguire, Joseph, "Far From Erne's Shore" [73880] (Decca 12261) (Disk XA78 1929)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph, "Whistler From Bawn" [63998] Side B: Maguire, Joseph, "My Charming Jenny Shea" [63997] (Decca 12163) (Disk XA78 2075)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph, "The County Tyrone" Side B: Maguire, Joseph, "By Kellis Water", undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Maguire, Joseph, [illegible], undated (Box 10, Box 4)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by Paddy Killoran's Quartet, "Rakes of Paddy Roe" [63155] Side B: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by Paddy Killoran's Quartet, "Star of Drum" [63156] (Decca 12160) (Disk XA78 785)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by Paddy Killoran's Quartet, "General Owen Roe" [63147] Side B: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by Paddy Killoran's Quartet, "Country Girl" [63184] (Decca 12137) (Disk XA78 829)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by Paddy Killoran's Quartet, "My Father's Cabin" [63153] Side B: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by Paddy Killoran's Quartet, "Rose of Ardee" [63154] (Decca 12151) (Disk XA78 1469)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by The Killoran Trio, "Pride of Glencoe" [62788] Side B: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by The Killoran Trio, "Braes of Strablane" [62783] (Decca 12133) (Disk XA78 827)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by The Killoran Trio, "By Lurgan Stream" [62785] Side B: Maguire, Joseph accompanied by The Killoran Trio, "Lovely Lough Erne" [62786] (Decca 12136) (Disk XA78 828)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph with Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "Kate From Ballinamore" [65253] Side B: Maguire, Joseph with Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "I Know a Church Crowned With Ivy" [65254] (Decca 12199) (Disk XA78 832)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph with Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "Dublin Brigade" [65259] Side B: Maguire, Joseph with Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "Round the Lovely Banks of Boyne" [65260] (Decca 12230) (Disk XA78 833)
  - Side A: Maguire, Joseph with Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "Soldiers of Old Ireland " [67827] Side B: Maguire, Joseph with Paddy Killoran's Orchestra, "At the Foot of Rooskey Hill" [67828] (Decca 12243) (Disk XA78 834)
  - Side A: Maguire, Leo, "Hills of Connemara" [OEP.145] Side B: Maguire, Leo, "Love Thee Dearest" [OEP.152] (Glenside W-118) (Disk XA78 837)
  - Side A: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.748] Side B: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.749] (London P.18236) (Disk XA78 802)
  - Side A: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.752] Side B: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.753] (London P.18238) (Disk XA78 803)
  - Side A: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.754] Side B: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.755] (London P.18239) (Disk XA78 804)
  - Side A: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.750] Side B: Maguire, Sean with Sean O'Driscoll, "Irish Country Dance Series" [MSC.751] (London P.18237) (Disk XA78 1486)
  - Side A: Mahoney, Jerry with Pat Fallon's Orchestra, "Patsy Fagan, the Dacent Irish Boy" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Mahoney, Jerry with Pat Fallon's Orchestra, "Mick McGilligan's Daughter, Mary Ann" [Matrix # not listed] (Celtic CI-1016) (Disk XA78 805)
  - Side A: Mahoney, Jerry with Pat Fallon's Orchestra, "My Old Skillara Hat" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Mahoney, Jerry with Pat Fallon's Orchestra, "O'Hara from Tara; McNamara from Mayo" [Matrix # not listed] (Celtic CI-1017) (Disk XA78 2077)
  - Side A: Malone, Danny, "Sweetheart Darlin'" [30-10888] Side B: Malone, Danny, "Love's Roses" [30-10889] (His Master's Voice B.4489) (Disk XA78 1230)
  - Side A: Malone, Danny, "There's a Cottage by the Shannon" [39106] Side B: Malone, Danny, "In the Valley Near Sleivenamon" [39108] (Decca 12043) (Disk XA78 1254)
  - Side A: Malone, Danny, "Low Backed Car" [39109] Side B: Malone, Danny, "Cockles and Mussels" [39110] (Decca 12025) (Disk XA78 1487)
  - Side A: Malone, Danny, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [30-10561] Side B: Malone, Danny, "Her Name Is Mary" [30-10562] (His Master's Voice B.4420) (Disk XA78 1488)
  - Side A: Malone, Danny, "I'll Take You Home Again Kathleen" [39107] Side B: Malone, Danny, "All That I Want Is in Ireland" [39111] (Decca 12052) (Disk XA78 2078)
  - Side A: Malone, Paddy and His Accordian Band, "Irish Reels" [GB.5336] Side B: Malone, Paddy and His Accordian Band, "Irish Jigs" [GB.5337] (Rex 15032) (Disk XA78 921)
  - Side A: Mariners, "Shannon, the Shamrocks and You" [CO 45176] Side B: Mariners, "And Then I Prayed" [CO 45177] (Columbia 39332) (Disk XA78 806)
  - Side A: Mariners, "Be the Good Lord Willing " [CO 41754] Side B: Locke, Joseph, "How Can You Buy Killarney?" [CO 41999] (Columbia Catalog # not listed) (Disk XA78 1489)
  - Side A: Marist Convent Choral Speaking Choir, "Congo" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Marist Convent Choral Speaking Choir, "Jim" [Matrix # not listed] (ALD357) (Disk XA78 925)
  - Side A: Marist Convent Choral TK, "Shepard" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Dandelion, "Morning and Evening" [Matrix # not listed] (ALD52) (Disk XA78 807)
  - Side A: Marks, Harry, "Cohen on the Telephone" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Kelly, John T., "Backyard Conversation Between Two Jealous Irish Washwomen" [Matrix # not listed] (Silvertone 5023) (Disk XA78 808)
  - Side A: Marsh, Howard, "Molly Brannigan" [79625] Side B: Marsh, Howard, "Ould Plaid Shawl" [79626] (Columbia A3435) (Disk XA78 1490)
  - Side A: Marsh, Howard, "Just We Two" [79524] Side B: Marsh, Howard, "Rose of Athlone" [79535] (Columbia A3357) (Disk XA78 1491)
  - Side A: Martin, Denis, "In the Heart of a Shamrock" [CE.12494] Side B: Martin, Denis, "How Can You Buy Killarney?" [CE.12495] (His Master's Voice I.P.502) (Disk XA78 1483)
  - Side A: Martin, Denis, "My Lagan Love" [CE.12346-1] Side B: Martin, Denis, "Rose of Mooncoin" [CE.12347-1] (His Master's Voice I.P.493) (Disk XA78 1484)
  - Side A: Martin, Denis, "Maureen Bawn" [CE.12296] Side B: Martin, Denis, "Killarney in the Spring" [CE.12297] (His Master's Voice I.P.475) (Disk XA78 1485)
  - Side A: Martin, Denis, "Believe Me If All Those Endearing Young Charms" [CE.12092] Side B: Martin, Denis, "Road to Ireland" [CE.12093] (His Master's Voice I.P.453) (Disk XA78 1492)
  - Side A: Martin, Eddie, "Mother in Ireland" [76489] Side B: Martin, Eddie, "Bells of St. Patrick's Cathedral" [76490] (Decca 12285) (Disk XA78 809)
  - Side A: Martin, Eddie, "I Looked at Norah " [76491] Side B: Martin, Eddie, "Come Back Paddy Reilly" [76492] (Decca 12286) (Disk XA78 810)
  - Side A: Martin, Freddy and His Orchestra, "Johnny Doughboy Found A Rose In Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Martin, Freddy and His Orchestra, "I'll Keep the Lovelight Burning " [Matrix # not listed] (Bluebird B-11503) (Disk XA78 2021)
  - Side A: Martin, Freddy and His Orchestra, "Miss You" [] Side B: Martin, Freddy and His Orchestra, "Rose O'Day" [] (Bluebird B-11286-B) (Disk XA78 2317)
  - Side A: Marvin, Johnny "The Ukelele Ace", "Hooray For the Irish!" [10852] Side B: Marvin, Johnny "The Ukelele Ace", "I Ain't in Love No More" [10853] (Edison 51707) (Disk XA78 1907)
  - Side A: Massed Brass Bands, "Under the Double Eagle" [R.2416D] Side B: Massed Brass Bands, "Sentry! Go By" [R.2417D] (Rex 15058), cuid36934 (Disk XA78 814)
  - Side A: Massed Brass Bands, "On the March" [W.6557] Side B: Massed Brass Bands, "Great Little Army" [W.6559] (Rex 15035) (Disk XA78 1482)
  - Side A: Matthews, Mike, "Waves of Tory" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Matthews, Mike, "Barn Dance" [Matrix # not listed] (Tara 430) (Disk XA78 811)
  - Side A: Matthews, Mike, "Highlands" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Matthews, Mike, "Polkas Majestic and O'Connors" [Matrix # not listed] (Tara 432) (Disk XA78 812)
  - Side A: Matthews, Mike, "Katie Connor" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Matthews, Mike, "Polka" [Matrix # not listed] (Tara 434) (Disk XA78 813)
  - Side A: Mattie Toohy's Irish Minstrels, "Minstrel's Fancy and the Smokey Chimney" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Mattie Toohy's Irish Minstrels, "Moonlight in Mayo and The Men of the West" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-206) (Disk XA78 931)
  - Side A: Mattie Toohy's Irish Minstrels, "Maid on the Green and The Three Little Drummers" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Mattie Toohy's Irish Minstrels, "Barren Rocks of Aden, All the Way to Dublin" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-207) (Disk XA78 932)
  - Side A: Mattie Toohy's Irish Minstrels, "First of May and the Green Fields of America" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Mattie Toohy's Irish Minstrels, "Wild Colonial Boy and A Mother's Love is a Blessing" [Matrix # not listed] (Copley 9-205) (Disk XA78 2089)
  - Side A: McAlpin, David, "Phil the Fluter's Ball" [WAR.60] Side B: McAlpin, David, "Master McGra" [WAR.63] (Regal Zonophone I.Z.144) (Disk XA78 1481)
  - Side A: McCafferty, James, "Donovans" [30-5696] Side B: McCafferty, James, "Slaney Side" [30-5697] (His Master's Voice I.P.129) (Disk XA78 786)
  - Side A: McCafferty, James, "Off to Philadelphia" [30-3346] Side B: McCafferty, James, "Kitty, My Love, Will You Marry Me?" [30-3349] (His Master's Voice I.M.404) (Disk XA78 817)
  - Side A: McCafferty, James, "Stuttering Lovers" [30-3347] Side B: McCafferty, James, "Spanish Lady" [30-3348] (His Master's Voice I.P.121) (Disk XA78 1478)
  - Side A: McCafferty, James, "Molly Brannigan" [30-5594] Side B: McCafferty, James, "Ninepenny Fidil" [30-5595] (His Master's Voice I.M.409) (Disk XA78 1479)
  - Side A: McCafferty, James, "Sailor Man" [GB.3839] Side B: McCafferty, James, "Heigh Ho! The Morning Dew" [GB.3840] (Decca F.2841) (Disk XA78 1480)
  - Side A: McCallum, Andy, "Old Stone Wall" [GB.6386] Side B: McCallum, Andy, "Load of Kale Plants" [GB.6391] (Decca F.3794) (Disk XA78 1477)
  - Side A: McCallum, David, "Bonnie Lass O'Bon Accord, The Muckin' o' Geordie's Byre, The 10 Pound Fiddle" [1533] Side B: McCallum, David, "Cam' Ye by Athol P, Cock o' the North, March" [1544] (Parlophone E3429) (Disk XA78 1243)
  - McCann, Jim and his Irish-Americans, "Irish Dance Festival", undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Side A: McCarthy, Pat, "My Galway Rose" [63490] Side B: McCarthy, Pat, "Off to Philadelphia" [63486] (Decca 12165) (Disk XA78 1475)
  - Side A: McCarthy, Pat, "My Mother's Rosary" [63492] Side B: McCarthy, Pat, "Smile Again, Kathleen Mavourneen" [63493] (Decca 12152) (Disk XA78 1476)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "Mother's Hands" [38] Side B: McClaskey, Harry, "Hiawatha's Melody of Love" [50] (Columbia 22356) (Disk XA78 787)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "Gypsy's Warning" [46246] Side B: McClaskey, Harry, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie" [46245] (Columbia A1913) (Disk XA78 1474)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "Somewhere a Voice is Calling" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: Baker, Elsie and Frederick Wheeler, "Maiden in Grey" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 17475) (Disk XA78 1634)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "Memories" [46273] Side B: McClaskey, Harry, "My Mother's Rosary" [Illegible] (Columbia Illegible) (Disk XA78 1635)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie" [46245] Side B: McClaskey, Harry, "Gypsy's Warning" [46246] (Columbia A 1913) (Disk XA78 1636)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 2389) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1876)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "My Mother's Rosary " [Matrix # not listed] (Silvertone 47092) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1880)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "Little Bit of Heaven" [80866 A] Side B: McClaskey, Harry, "Mighty Lak' a Rose" [80866 B] (Pathe 29123) 12 Inch (Disk XA78 2244)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [E.65475] Side B: Reynolds, Harry, "Devon for Me" [A.93337] (Pathe 29166) 12 Inch (Disk XA78 2274)
  - Side A: McClaskey, Harry, "Where the River Shannon Flows" Side B: Harry Reynolds, "West Country Song, "Devon For Me"", undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Side A: McConnell's Four Leaf Shamrocks, "Favorite Irish Jigs" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McConnell's Four Leaf Shamrocks, "Favorite Irish Reels" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 19446) (Disk XA78 2076)
  - Side A: McCool, James, "Low Back'd Car" [4389] Side B: Jones, Ada and Len Spencer, "Mr. and Mrs. Murphy" [4400] (Victor 16100) (Disk XA78 1472)
  - Side A: McCool, James, "Meeting of the Waters " [132789] (Victor 64622) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1473)
  - Side A: McCormack, John and Fritz Kreisler, "Flirtation [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2368)
  - Side A: McCormack, John and Fritz Kreisler, "Flirtation [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2342)
  - Side A: McCormack, John and Fritz Kreisler, "Tales of Hoffman-Barcarolle [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2365)
  - Side A: McCormack, John and Fritz Kreisler, "Tales of Hoffman-Barcarolle [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2380)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Ben Bolt [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2369)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Macushla " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64257) One-Sided (Disk XA78 50)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Rosary " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64426) One-Sided (Disk XA78 51)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "My Wild Irish Rose " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64428) One-Sided (Disk XA78 63)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Beautiful Isle of Somewhere " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64559) One-Sided (Disk XA78 64)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Old Refrain " [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64664) One-Sided (Disk XA78 65)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Star Spangled Banner " [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64205) One-Sided (Disk XA78 66)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "That Tumble Down Shack in Athlone" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Mother in Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 785) (Disk XA78 67)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "It's a Long, Long Way to Tipperary" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Vacant Chair" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 896) (Disk XA78 68)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Macushla" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64311) One-Sided (Disk XA78 69)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64405) One-Sided (Disk XA78 70)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Somewhere a Voice is Calling" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64837) One-Sided (Disk XA78 71)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "That Tumble-Down Shack in Athlone" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64860) One-Sided (Disk XA78 72)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Your Eyes Have Told Me So" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64913) One-Sided (Disk XA78 73)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Just a Cottage Small" [] Side B: McCormack, John, "Through All the Days to Be" [] (Victrola 1133-B) (Disk XA78 2375)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64982) One-Sided (Disk XA78 74)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Learn to Smile" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64994) One-Sided (Disk XA78 101)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Because I Love You" [] Side B: McCormack, John, "Far-Away Bells" [] (Victrola 1215-B) (Disk XA78 2377)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Little Town in the Ould County Down" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 66012) One-Sided (Disk XA78 102)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Rose of My Heart" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 66028) One-Sided (Disk XA78 103)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Sweet Peggy O'Neal" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 66112) One-Sided (Disk XA78 104)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Little Mother of Mine [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2372)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Mother in Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 17898) One-Sided (Disk XA78 105)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "When You Look in the Heart of a Rose [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2378)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Annie Laurie" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Auld Scotch Sangs " [Matrix # not listed] (RCA Victor 1305) (Disk XA78 788)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Dear Old Pal of Mine" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 4571) One-Sided (Disk XA78 880)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Star Spangled Banner" [Matrix # not listed] (Columbia 3484) One-Sided (Disk XA78 948)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Marcheta" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Somewhere a Voice Is Calling" [Matrix # not listed] (RCA Victor 1247) (Disk XA78 1470)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Ireland, Mother Ireland" [A.55192] Side B: McCormack, John, "Rose of Tralee" [A.58586] (His Master's Voice I.R.202) (Disk XA78 1471)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Sunshine of Your Smile" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64341) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1493)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Eilleen Allanna" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64309) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1494)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Sweet Genevieve" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64302) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1495)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "When Twilight Comes, I'm Thinking of You" [] Side B: McCormack, John, "Calling Me Back to You" [] (Victrola 1197-B) (Disk XA78 2379)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "At Dawning" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64180) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1496)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Believe Me if All Those Endearing Young Charms" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64694) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1497)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" [A6RB-0001] Side B: McCormack, John, "Mother Machree" [B7RB-0003] (RCA Victor 410-0172) (Disk XA78 1498)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "There's a Long, Long Trail" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64622) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1499)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Sunshine of Your Smile" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64426) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1500)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "My Wild Irish Rose" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64665) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1501)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Rose of Tralee" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Ireland, Mother Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 1452) (Disk XA78 1502)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Silver Threads Among the Gold" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "When You and I Were Young Maggie" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 1173) (Disk XA78 1503)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Somewhere in the World" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Where the Rainbow Ends " [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 968) (Disk XA78 1504)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "My Wild Irish Rose" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Bonnie Wee Thing" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 895) (Disk XA78 1505)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Mother Machree" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Little Bit of Heaven" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 768) (Disk XA78 1506)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Ireland My Sireland" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64631) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1507)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "When Irish Eyes are Smiling" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64622) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1508)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Lord is My Light [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2400)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Sunshine of Your Smile" [Matrix # not listed] ( 64476) One-Sided, 1908-1912 (Disk XA78 1509)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Tis an Irish Girl I Love and She's Just Like You" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64796) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1519)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "My Irish Song of Songs" [Matrix # not listed] (Columbia 3500) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1520)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Harp That Once Thro' Tara's Halls" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Garden Where the Praities Grow" [Matrix # not listed] (RCA Victor 1553) (Disk XA78 1633)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64311) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1868)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Where the River Shannon Flows" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64818) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1869)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Calling Me Home to You [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2376)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Only You [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2381)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Remember the Rose" [] Side B: McCormack, John, "Sometime You'll Remember" [] (Victrola 918-B) (Disk XA78 2373)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "First Rose of Summer" [Matrix # not listed] (Silvertone 19818) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1871)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Mother Machree" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64696) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1912)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Kathleen Mavourneen" [] Side B: McCormack, John, "Killarney" [] (Victrola 6199-B) (Disk XA78 2329)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Keep the Home Fire Burning" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 64120) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1913)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Road That Brought You to Me [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2374)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Low-Back'd Car [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2435)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "I Hear You Calling Me" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 60129) One-Sided (Disk XA78 1915)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Rose of Tralee" [Matrix # not listed] Side B: McCormack, John, "Ireland, Mother Ireland" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 1452) (Disk XA78 1955)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Little Bit of Heaven" [Matrix # not listed] (Victor 5149) One-Sided (Disk XA78 2006)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Mother Machree" [Matrix # not listed] (Victrola 64411) One-Sided (Disk XA78 2054)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Asthore [One-sided]" [] Side B:, "Blank" [] ( ) (Disk XA78 2389)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "At Dawning" [] Side B: McCormack, John, "I Hear a Thrush at Eve" [] (Victrola 742-B) (Disk XA78 2363)
  - Side A: McCormack, John, "Silver Threads Among the Gold" [] Side B: McCormack, John, "When You and I Were Young, Maggie" [] (Victrola 781-B) (Disk XA78 2366)